

## Profile

Software engineering manager always looking for self-improvement, with 2+ years of engineer management experience and 9+ years of software development experience. Dedicated to leveling up engineers and guiding a project to success with my experience in full development life-cycles across several mobile games, and collaborating with other disciplines.

# Employment History

## **Engineering Manager at Zynga, Toronto**

January 2019 — Present

Working with a small group of software engineers over 2 game teams:

- Coaching and growing their skill sets and providing paths for career growth
- Recruiting and leveling up the team Writing tech specs and participating in development efforts alongside them
- Identifying complications or hurdles in the team/game pipelines and making improvements
- Collaborating across other teams and disciplines

## Senior Software Engineer at Zynga, Toronto

July 2013 — December 2018

Working in agile-like processes to ship game client updates for several mobile game projects

- Full development life-cycle: design, implementation, testing, release & support
- Coordinating feature experimentation
- Reacting to game metrics and app health analysis
- Working with product management to realize their vision
- · Recruiting and mentoring interns

# Software Engineer at Zynga, Toronto

July 2011 — June 2013

Working under senior staff direction across a few mobile game projects

- · Feature implementation
- Feature iterations
- · Bug fixes and patches

## Education

Computer Science with Software Engineering Option, University of Waterloo, Waterloo

September 2006 — April 2011

## References

References available upon request

### **Details**

Mississauga, Canada, +1 (647)-823-8395 howling.ape@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

**Android Development** 

iOS Development
Unity
ReactiveX
GitHub
Java
Kotlin
Objective-C
Swift

# C#

JavaScript

Ruby

### **Hobbies**

Karate, Sumo, Longboarding, Gaming, Music Production